Hello friends, I am Namkeen present in front of you
with information. Today we are going to
tell you about car insurance,
which we have covered earlier as well.
What is the benefit of invoice cover and what is the benefit if you
take other advances along with it. What is the
benefit of key replacement and
if you take other advances along with it, then
what is its benefit. Today
we are going to tell you that there is
also
an add on in the name of key replacement that if you lose your key, then
you will get it free of post.
You will not have to pay any charges
and it will be provided to you by the company.
And if any of
your car locks is damaged, then there is
any repair charge for it, then
it will be paid by the company. Friends,
this is the benefit of key replacement.
Secondly, I would like to tell you about another add on in this,
one is NCB protection.
Friends, it is important to tell you this because
when we renew any insurance,
I have
seen for myself that till I  There was no urgency with this company or any other
company, then I also used to
think that whatever insurance we get at the lowest price,
we should take that only for formalities,
but friends, we should
always keep the Aadols in mind, Aadol
always gives us benefits.